<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Florian Wechsung</title>
    <link>https://florianwechsung.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Florian Wechsung</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://florianwechsung.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://florianwechsung.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://florianwechsung.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Submitted Fireshape: a shape optimization toolbox for Firedrake, Alberto Paganini, Florian Wechsung.
Shape optimisation for faster washout in recirculating flows, Jessica G. Williams, Florian Wechsung, Ben W. Turney, Sarah L. Waters, Derek E. Moulton.
A Reynolds-robust preconditioner for the Reynolds-robust Scott-Vogelius discretization of the stationary incompressible Navier-Stokes equations, Patrick E Farrell, Lawrence Mitchell, L Ridgway Scott, Florian Wechsung.
Augmented Lagrangian preconditioners for the Oseen-Frank model of cholesteric liquid crystals, Jingmin Xia, Patrick E Farrell, Florian Wechsung.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://florianwechsung.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://florianwechsung.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description> Spring term 2019, Tutor for Mathematical Models of Financial Derivatives, University of Oxford. Fall term 2017, Instructor for Modelling, analysis and computation of continuous real world problems, University of Oxford. Spring term 2017, Teaching assistant for Mathematical Models of Financial Derivatives, University of Oxford. Fall term 2016, Teaching assistant for Viscous Flow, University of Oxford. Fall term 2014, Tutor for Introduction to Probability, University of Bonn.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>