<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Florian Wechsung</title>
    <link>https://florianwechsung.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Florian Wechsung</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language><atom:link href="https://florianwechsung.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://florianwechsung.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://florianwechsung.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Submitted A-posteriori optimization for increasing manufacturing tolerances in stellarator coil design, Florian Wechsung, Andrew Giuliani, Matt Landreman, Antoine Cerfon, Georg Stadler.
Direct computation of magnetic surfaces in Boozer coordinates and coil optimization for quasi-symmetry, Andrew Giuliani, Florian Wechsung, Matt Landreman, Georg Stadler, Antoine Cerfon.
Published / Accepted Precise stellarator quasi-symmetry can be achieved with electromagnetic coils, Florian Wechsung, Matt Landreman, Andrew Giuliani, Antoine Cerfon, Georg Stadler, Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, 2022 .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://florianwechsung.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://florianwechsung.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Spring term 2021, Lecturer for Numerical Analysis, New York University.
Spring term 2019, Tutor for Mathematical Models of Financial Derivatives, University of Oxford.
Fall term 2017, Instructor for Modelling, analysis and computation of continuous real world problems, University of Oxford.
Spring term 2017, Teaching assistant for Mathematical Models of Financial Derivatives, University of Oxford.
Fall term 2016, Teaching assistant for Viscous Flow, University of Oxford.
Fall term 2014, Tutor for Introduction to Probability, University of Bonn.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
